I like it here.
ここが好きなんだね
What have you done?
何したことある?
Not really.
ないね
I want to?
したい?
No, that's it.
いや、そんな
I want to try it.
してみたいんだよね
No, that's it.
いや、そんな
I've never done it.
した ことない
Yes, he said he wanted to.
そうだ、したいって言われた
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
No, no, I have to thank you too.
違う違う、おじさんもお礼しなきゃいけないから
I have to thank you, my butt.
お礼しなきゃ、お尻も
If you don't thank me, I'll give you my butt too.
お 礼 し な き ゃ、 お尻も
I have to thank you, my butt.
お礼しなきゃ、お尻も
If you don't thank me, I'll give you my butt too.
お 礼 し な き ゃ、 お 尻も
I'm crying.
泣いてる
delicious.
おいしい
It's very delicious.
すごくおいしい
I was in it, I was in it.
座入ってたね、座入ってた
So, would you like me to remove it?
じゃあ、抜いてもらう?
Wow, that's amazing.
うわ、すっごいしまう
oh yeah.
そうそう
What's that sound?
何の音してるの?